{
  "GroupId": 3,
  "GroupName": "CHEFS LIFE",
  "Levels": [
    {
      "GroupId": 3,
      "LevelId": 1,
      "Questions": [
        {
          "level_image": 3,
          "answer_text": "AUGUST",
          "question": "During this month, summer heat reaches its peak, inspiring vacations"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 3,
          "answer_text": "COUPON",
          "question": "Hand this over to save money on your purchase"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 3,
          "answer_text": "LAYOUT",
          "question": "Blueprint for organization, where elements find their perfect place"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 4,
          "answer_text": "CURFEW",
          "question": "when the streets empty and doors lock, it's time to stay indoors."
        },
        {
          "level_image": 4,
          "answer_text": "ACTION",
          "question": "it's the heartbeat of every thrilling plot and the catalyst for change."
        },
        {
          "level_image": 4,
          "answer_text": "CINEMA",
          "question": "Where dreams flicker to life, on a silver screen, in the dark"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 4,
          "answer_text": "GLORIA",
          "question": "Her name echoes triumph, a melody of resilience and strength"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 4,
          "answer_text": "ARTIST",
          "question": "Creator of worlds with brush or pen"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 0,
          "answer_text": "GUY FIERI",
          "question": null
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "GroupId": 3,
      "LevelId": 2,
      "Questions": [
        {
          "level_image": 3,
          "answer_text": "WESTREN",
          "question": "Where tumbleweeds dance and gunslingers roam"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 3,
          "answer_text": "PHOENIX",
          "question": "Rising from ashes, a symbol of rebirth and renewal"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 3,
          "answer_text": "STUDENT",
          "question": "Eager learner, navigating halls of knowledge"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 3,
          "answer_text": "VISIBLE",
          "question": "Seen by all, yet sometimes overlooked"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 4,
          "answer_text": "COUCHED",
          "question": "Words artfully hidden within, waiting to be uncovered like treasures"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 4,
          "answer_text": "CASHBOX",
          "question": "Where earnings gather for safekeeping"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 4,
          "answer_text": "PIGEONS",
          "question": "they coo softly while weaving through city streets"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 4,
          "answer_text": "SURFACE",
          "question": "A boundary between air and earth"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 0,
          "answer_text": "SOUS CHEF",
          "question": null
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "GroupId": 3,
      "LevelId": 3,
      "Questions": [
        {
          "level_image": 2,
          "answer_text": "CHILD",
          "question": "Tiny explorer, with eyes wide in wonder"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 2,
          "answer_text": "PEACE",
          "question": "The absence of conflict, where tranquility whispers"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 2,
          "answer_text": "BACON",
          "question": "Sizzling delight, from pig to plate, a crispy indulgence loved by many."
        },
        {
          "level_image": 2,
          "answer_text": "IDEAL",
          "question": "Perfection's distant echo, guiding aspirations toward a better tomorrow"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 3,
          "answer_text": "RECAP",
          "question": "Summarizing journey's steps, a quick rewind through the highlights of the day."
        },
        {
          "level_image": 3,
          "answer_text": "YAHOO",
          "question": "An exclamation of joy or a pioneering internet search engine"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 3,
          "answer_text": "AGENT",
          "question": "Silent sentinel of secrecy"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 3,
          "answer_text": "BEEFS",
          "question": "Tender cuts of contention, simmering with disagreement"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 0,
          "answer_text": "HEAD CHEF",
          "question": null
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "GroupId": 3,
      "LevelId": 4,
      "Questions": [
        {
          "level_image": 1,
          "answer_text": "SANDAL",
          "question": "Open-toed comfort, embraced by sun-kissed feet"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 1,
          "answer_text": "UNITED",
          "question": "In harmony we stand, diverse yet bonded"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 1,
          "answer_text": "NATURE",
          "question": "Life's canvas, painted with hues of green and blue"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 1,
          "answer_text": "NEEDLE",
          "question": "Thread's faithful guide, piercing through layers with precision"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 1,
          "answer_text": "YAWING",
          "question": "A sleepy reflex, where mouths stretch wide"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 2,
          "answer_text": "BACKUP",
          "question": "Digital safety net, guarding against loss"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 2,
          "answer_text": "ENERGY",
          "question": "The invisible fuel, powering life's dance"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 2,
          "answer_text": "EDITOR",
          "question": "Guardian of words, sculptor of stories"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 2,
          "answer_text": "HEALTH",
          "question": "Body's balance, mind's sanctuary"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 2,
          "answer_text": "BRIDAL",
          "question": "The dawn of forever, where vows intertwine"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 2,
          "answer_text": "ISLAND",
          "question": "Earth's lonely jewels, cradled by the ocean"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 2,
          "answer_text": "BOARDS",
          "question": "Stepping stones of decisions, where strategies are laid"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 2,
          "answer_text": "ENDURE",
          "question": "Strength's silent anthem, echoing resilience through trials"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 0,
          "answer_text": "Sunny Anderson",
          "question": null
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "GroupId": 3,
      "LevelId": 5,
      "Questions": [
        {
          "level_image": 5,
          "answer_text": "COUNCIL",
          "question": "Assembly of minds, where decisions take flight"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 5,
          "answer_text": "COTTAGE",
          "question": "Charming abode, tucked away in nature's embrace,"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 5,
          "answer_text": "COUNTRY",
          "question": "Vast landscapes unfold, where cultures bloom"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 6,
          "answer_text": "FINANCE",
          "question": "Numbers dance in harmony, orchestrating the symphony of wealth"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 6,
          "answer_text": "DESKTOP",
          "question": "Digital command center, where pixels paint productivity"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 6,
          "answer_text": "ICEBERG",
          "question": "Majestic behemoth, its tip reveals the tale"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 6,
          "answer_text": "HANDBAG",
          "question": "Stylish companion, carrying life's essentials"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 0,
          "answer_text": "Cat Cora",
          "question": null
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}